<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Aaryan&#39;s 📖</title>
    <link>/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Aaryan&#39;s 📖</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:49:17 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>No Collision Guarantee</title>
      <link>/posts/no-collision-guaranteed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jan 2022 17:49:17 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/no-collision-guaranteed/</guid>
      <description>Designing No Collision Guarantee System. So for the past few days, I&amp;rsquo;ve been trying to build a distributed highly scalable, no collision guaranteed URL shortening service.
The Architecture So if you pass in a long url called https://longurl.com, the backend will send you a short url that would be unique to each request, and the structure of the url would look something like: https://shorturl.com/[slug].
The slug is our main component, it should always be unique.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Visual Regression Testing of Ceph Dashboard</title>
      <link>/posts/gsoc_with_ceph/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Sep 2021 17:10:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/gsoc_with_ceph/</guid>
      <description>This summer I worked with The Ceph Foundation under Google Summer Of Code &amp;lsquo;21 (GSoC) programme.
Google Summer of Code is a global program focused on bringing more student developers into open source software development. Students work with an open source organization on a 10 week programming project during their break from school.
In this blog, I&amp;rsquo;ll share my journey of completing the project &amp;ldquo;Visual Regression Testing of Ceph Dashboard&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Type Coercion In JavaScript</title>
      <link>/posts/type-coercion-javascript/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Jun 2021 04:57:26 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/type-coercion-javascript/</guid>
      <description>This small blog was sparked by a post that I saw: There are many posts like the above on the internet, and almost all of them are because of this type coercion thingy. So in this blog, I&amp;rsquo;m gonna try to explain what type coercion is and what&amp;rsquo;s happening in that post 😉.
What is type coercion? There are 6 primitive data types in JavaScript: undefined, Boolean, Number, String, BigInt and Symbol.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Node.js To The Moon 🚀</title>
      <link>/posts/scaling-your-node.js-app-like-a-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 May 2021 19:12:41 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/scaling-your-node.js-app-like-a-boss/</guid>
      <description>Scaling your Node.js app like a boss Is Node even Node, if you&amp;rsquo;re not running a Node process on every CPU core of your machine 😁?
So a little history: JavaScript was created out of the rapidly growing demand for dynamic content on the web, it was designed to do simple things like creating a colourful mouse trail or to validate forms. It was only in 2009 that Ryan Dahl, creator of Node.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My First Post</title>
      <link>/posts/my-first-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Apr 2021 17:10:16 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/my-first-post/</guid>
      <description>Welcome Yes, if you can see this, you&amp;rsquo;re seeing my first post where I painfully spent hours trying to set up hugo and tweaked to my liking💖!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
